Select Page

Privacy Policy
==============

**Privacy Policy:**

We value your trust and understand the importance of protecting your personal information. This privacy policy outlines how **Mynextpay** ensures the security and confidentiality of your data. 

By using our services, you agree to the practices described herein.

1. **Information Security:**

**Mynextpay** is committed to maintaining a secure internet environment for all our customers. We employ industry-standard SSL encryption, ensuring that your personal and banking information is transmitted securely, just like the banks do. Our security measures are continuously updated to safeguard the privacy of our customers’ data.

**2\. Internal Limited Access:**

Access to your information is restricted to authorized staff members and managers only. All our employees undergo rigorous background checks before being granted access to customer data. This limited access ensures that your information is safeguarded and used solely for the specific purposes for which it is required, such as processing loan applications, improving our services, evaluating creditworthiness, and providing customer support.

**3\. Sharing Data with Third Parties:**

In order to facilitate loan processing, manage your accounts, and enhance our services, we may share your personal information with carefully selected third-party lenders, financial institutions, credit bureaus, debt collectors, marketing partners, and other relevant entities. These parties have committed to upholding the confidentiality and security of your data and will utilize it solely for the purpose of evaluating your loan application or providing related services.

**AppHub Data Sharing:**

When you submit information through AppHub, it is shared with multiple lenders and/or brokerages to optimize the success of your loan approval. You can view the list of vendors here: [**Third Party Information**](https://mynextpay.ca/third-party-information/). Please note that this data is stored outside of the province of Quebec. Our vendors and their partners may contact you via email, phone, or SMS (standard messaging rates may apply, varying by carrier). You have the option to opt out at any time by texting HELP for assistance or STOP to cancel.

 4. **Phone call, SMS Consent:**

By providing your phone number to **Mynextpay** , you consent to receive calls and/or SMS messages from us. These messages may include transactional notifications, account updates, customer surveys, or other relevant information about your application or account with **Mynextpay** .  
You have the right to revoke your consent for receiving calls or SMS messages at any time. To opt-out or unsubscribe, please follow the instructions provided in the SMS messages or contact us using the information below.

**5\. Email Consent:**

By providing your email address to **Mynextpay** , you consent to receive emails from us. These emails may include transactional communications, promotional offers, account updates, customer surveys, or other relevant information about your application or account with **Mynextpay** .  
You have the right to revoke your consent for receiving emails at any time. To opt-out or unsubscribe, you can use the “Unsubscribe” link provided in our emails or contact us using the information below.

6. **Data Retention:**

We will retain your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this policy, or as required by applicable laws and regulations. If you wish to have your data deleted, please contact us using the information below.

7. **User Rights:**

You have the right to access, rectify, and delete your personal information held by My Next Pay. If you would like to exercise any of these rights or have questions about your data, please contact us using the information provided below.

8. **Cookies and Tracking:**

My Next Pay may use cookies and similar tracking technologies to enhance your browsing experience and gather information about how you use our website. For more details, please review our [Cookie Policy](https://mynextpay.ca/cookie-policy/)**.**

**Contact Information:**

If you have any questions, concerns, or requests related to your privacy or this policy, please don’t hesitate to contact us:

Support: info@mynextpay.ca

With over 12 years of experience, Mynextpay, provides quick financial solutions to its Canadian clients. Our quick cash loan program is quick and convenient. Even if your previous credit history is not perfect, My Next Pay strives to provide every customer with a short term cash loan that is suitable for your budget.

Talk about fast cash! With our e-mail money transfer we can get you a cash advance in minutes! Contact one of our agents for an appointment or contact us online now!

Services

Legal & More

Contact Us

Email: info@mynextpay.ca

6000 Cote des Neiges, Suite 370  
Montreal, QC  
H3S1Z8

Copyright © 2021 – Mynextpay. All Right Reserved

[

](https://mexxusmedia.com/?mynextpay)
